SHAILESH BHAT

A/7402, Adwait Chs, Star colony, Manpada road, Dombivili East, Thane, Maharashtra, India-421204
amshaileshpayments@gmail.com



View my portfolio at http://amshailesh.github.io

Sı	um	ım	aı	rv
_				- ,

Hi, my name is Shailesh Manjunath Bhat. A graduate in Bachelor of Science in Information Technology from Mumbai University. Living in Dombivili, Maharashtra, India, Earth, Rodinia. Born on 18th February 1989, i am 31 years young now. I have learnt HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, PHP & MySQL from Seed Infotech, Thane; from November 2019 to June 2020. Before 2019, from June 2011 to Oct 2019 i was working in E-Commerce Industry. Starting from June 2011 i worked for Naaptol Online Shopping Pvt td, Just buy Live Pvt Ltd, Maayra Retail Pvt Ltd & Lumina Datamatics pvt Ltd.

	Education
2009 - 2011	Attempted to study M.Sc. IT Model College Result Failed
2006 - 2009	B.Sc IT Mumbai University Result Passed
	Skills —
HTML5, CSS3, Javasc PHP, MySQL	Cript, JQuery, Web Development
	Work experience
Nov 2019 - Present	Studying Full Stack Web Development Seed Infotech, Thane

Studied till now HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, PHP, MySQL.

Selling electronic devices & Cloths online. Listing on Amazon, Flipkart. Order Processing. Dispatch.

Own Business as Amazon Seller

Monthlyfair

Customer service.

Feb 2019 - Oct 2019

JAN 2018 - Oct 2018

Group Leader Amazon US Process

Lumina Datamatics Private Limited

Work for Amazon US process. Finding Exact & alternate products. Comparing Exact & Alternate products. Entering details inhouse portal. Quality check. Assigning Work to team members. Weekly Review of performance of team members.

AUG 2016 - DEC 2017

Uploads In-Charge

Maayra Retail Pvt Ltd

Monitoring Uploads Reporting Listings status on individual websites to CEO. Maintaining updated catalog in Top 25 websites like Amazon India, UK, US, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Shopclues & Paytm, Limeroad etc. Coordinating with the procurement team for new products data. Uploading new products on marketplaces Amazon India, UK, US, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Shopclues & Paytm, Limeroad etc. Updating prices, Inventory, images, keywords etc

SEPT 2015 - May 2016

Worked as Listing executive

Just Buy Live Enterprise Pvt. Ltd

Adding new products. Maintaining updated online catalog. Responsible for maintenance of the website, Product updates, Offer Update, updating prices, stocks, writing reviews, uploading banners.

JUNE 2011 - Sept 2015 Executive Catalogue management Naaptol Club at Naaptol

Naaptol Online Shopping Pvt Ltd

Adding new products. Maintaining updated online catalog. Responsible for maintenance of the website, Product updates, Offer Update, updating prices, stocks, writing reviews, uploading banners.

Portfolio

Please visit https://amshailesh.github.io/ to view portfolio

(Tea manufacturer company, Badlapur. www.vedantcommodities.com) (Interior Designer, Dombivili. www.wallkeepers.in) (Chirantan Sanmitra Trust, Mulund. Chirantan Sanmitra Trust) (Alliance Wallpaper, Dombivili. Alliance Wallpaper)

